Janine Alyssa Freeze

Click here for my portfolio | 864-451-1607 | janinefreeze@gmail.com 4 Morningside Drive, Greenville, SC 29605

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am a Graphic Designer with 5+ years of experience in the field looking to use my expertise to create strong work with a clear message. Learning current marketing and design techniques to create relevant and effective designs for multiple purposes.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Suite
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap experience.
- GA4 Google Analytics/Google Tag Manager
- Social Media/Content Creation

SOFT SKILLS

- Attentive to detail
- Interpersonal/Communicative
- Critical Thinker/Problem solver
- Ability to work independently or with a team
- Self-motivated and highly teachable

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, OUTREACH CHURCH; GREENVILLE, SC — 6/2019-3/2021

- Regularly created both digital and printed media for Outreach Church's various events
- Created logos and illustrations (posters, coloring pages) for the Kid's Ministry
- Modified Outreach Church's logo to include variations for different ministries within the church
- Modified and maintained the church's website

CLOTHING PROCESSOR, MIRACLE HILL; GREENVILLE, SC — 11/2016-12/2017

• Processed all incoming clothing donations and categorizes them into types of clothing, seasons and holidays.

COMMUNICATIONS ASSOCIATE, HOLDEN VILLAGE; CHELAN, WA — 05/2013-05/2014

- Cooperated as a member of an in-house team to communicate news about Holden Village, a retreat center in the Cascade mountains, to the outside world
- Managed and created content for Holden's website and official Facebook page
- Assisted in the creation of various media, such as "The Village Voice" a quarterly print publication, and "Beholden," Holden Village's monthly e-newsletter.
- Created promotional materials for various events within and outside of Holden Village
- Produced logos, photos and other materials for usage in various media

GRAPHIC DESIGNER/CUSTOMER REP, SNEHTA; DULUTH, GA — 08/2012-05/2013

- Worked with a custom CMS tool to create websites for company clients
- Maintained client's websites and made changes when specified
- Created and maintained social media accounts for clients
- Created logos based on client's expectations
- Communicated with clients quickly and effectively
- Managed multiple projects in a fast-paced environment

EDUCATION

WESTWOOD COLLEGE, ATLANTA, GA — AAS, GRAPHIC DESIGN & MULTIMEDIA '12

REFERENCES

References available upon request.